see we've got about another 30 seconds
看到我们还有大约30秒
before the time but just out of interest
在时间之前但只是出于兴趣
how many of you are how many how many of
你们几个是多少个
you have this is the first Java one
你有这是第一个Java人
they've ever been to cool how many have
他们曾经去冷却过多少
been to a previous the other one okay so
以前去过另一个人所以
um audio can you test for the back can
音频，您可以测试后盖吗
you guys hear me better now in the back
你们现在在后面听到我更好
I'll try if I speak louder does it reach
我会大声说一声达到
okay I'll try and do a little louder on
好吧，我会尝试大声一点
the voice but if you can pick it up a
声音，但是如果你能接听的话
little there because that's above normal
那里很少，因为那高于正常水平
well it's good to see so many fresh
好，看到这么多新鲜
first time in Java one people that's an
第一次使用Java是一个
interesting mix for the audience usually
通常为观众带来有趣的组合
we get about a 3/4 to 1/4 ratio but this
我们得到大约3/4到1/4的比例，但是
is good subject we're gonna talk about
是我们要谈论的好话题
is right up there hopefully you're in
就在那儿，希望你在
the right room
合适的房间
I'm guilt na we're talking about garbage
我很内na，我们在谈论垃圾
collection in Java and just to set the
Java中的集合，仅用于设置
right expectation for the for the top
对顶部的正确期望
there's a little bit of echo at least
至少有一点回声
for me to set the right expectations for
给我树立正确​​的期望
the talk this is not a a how to tune GC
谈论这不是一个如何调整GC
talk this talk is focused on how GC
谈论本演讲重点在于GC
works how the machine works or how the
工作机器的工作方式或
mechanisms work and the idea is that if
机制起作用，想法是，如果
you can understand what garbage
你能明白什么垃圾
collection doesn't general in the
集合在
various stages and techniques
各个阶段和技术
terminologies and then you can apply
术语，然后您可以申请
your own brain to the tuning exercises
您自己的大脑进行调音练习
really so rather than giving you a set
真的是这样，而不是给你一套
of flags given that are good for 2017
给出的对2017年有利的标志
for a specific collective a specific
对于一个特定的集体
version of Java and a specific version
Java版本和特定版本
of your application I'm gonna try and
您将要尝试的
get you a feel for what garbage
让您感觉什么垃圾
collection actually behave like so you
集合实际上就像这样
could do the job on a regular basis so
可以定期做这项工作
now that's the real purpose here you
现在这才是真正的目的
learn enough to be dangerous and then
学会足够的危险，然后
you will get dangerous and that'll come
你会变得危险，那会来
with pain later
后来痛苦
um now my work in a company that makes
现在我在一家公司工作
JVMs and garbage collectors so I'm
JVM和垃圾收集器，所以我
really really proud of that and I
我为此感到非常自豪
promise that I will keep that part we
保证我会保留那一部分
make the best garbage collected on earth
使地球上收集的最好的垃圾
pretty much to the end there will be a
到最后几乎会有一个
lot of generic useful education here
这里有很多普通的有用的教育
that's good for any GPM or any garbage
这对任何GPM或任何垃圾都是有好处的
collector actually in the runtime so
收集器实际上是在运行时
agenda why it's the way we're going to
议程为什么这就是我们要去的方式
cover this is we'll start with
涵盖这是我们将从
fundamentals terminology and mechanisms
基本原理术语和机制
will then go and classify all the
然后将其分类
currently available production garbage
当前可用的生产垃圾
collectors in Jamie on most of them and
杰米（Jamie）的收藏家大部分
then we'll talk about to stop the world
那么我们将谈论停止世界
problem thank you this was no
问题谢谢你这不是
prescription and didn't talk about you
处方，没有谈论你
know what a world where that is salt man
知道那个盐人的世界
doesn't have it anymore
不再有
which like I said I'll keep that in the
就像我说的那样，我会将其保留在
middle about me my name is Gil Timmy I'm
关于我的中间我的名字叫吉尔·蒂米我
the CTO at is all systems I've been
我曾经去过的所有系统的CTO
working on garbage collection as a
从事垃圾收集工作
problem for around 15 years now and
大约15年以来的问题
here's some evidence of me working
这是我工作的一些证据
for those who don't recognize that
对于那些谁不知道
that's a trash compactor that's in my
那是我里面的垃圾压实机
kitchen the job of the trash compactor
厨房垃圾压实机的工作
if you think about it is to perform
如果你认为这是执行
minor GC compactions during the week so
在一周内进行少量的GC压实，因此
you only do a full GC evacuation once a
您一次只能进行一次完全的GC疏散
week that works great here in cut point
切点在这里效果很好的一周
at least then this isn't stopped working
至少然后这不会停止工作
there was a bug in it you can see the
有一个错误，您可以看到
fragments were falling out the building
碎片从建筑物上掉下来
open that actually happened I thought it
打开实际上发生的事，我以为是
would be funny to take a picture with
拍张照片会很有趣
the actual garbage collection book but
实际的垃圾收集书，但是
the most important thing about this
最重要的是
picture is that it was taken in lazy and
图片是它是偷懒地拍摄的
I recycle and I need new pictures I used
我回收并需要使用的新照片
to look better so I've worked in various
看起来更好，所以我从事过各种工作
garbage collectors including our garbage
垃圾收集器，包括我们的垃圾
collector called c4
收藏家叫c4
and a process collector I built a lot of
和一个过程收集器，我建立了很多
things physical machines virtual
物联网虚拟机
machines that help design CPU
有助于设计CPU的机器
instruction sets and operating systems
指令集和操作系统
and driver ISM runtimes obviously all
和驱动程序ISM运行时显然都是
the way up to nation scale enterprise
通往全国规模企业的道路
applications with tens of millions of
数以千万计的应用程序
subscribers all that comes with that so
订户附带的所有内容
I've made a lot of mistakes that some of
我犯了很多错误，
those that I teach people about but
那些我教过的人
unfortunately not you know people
不幸的是你不认识别人
usually learn from their own mistakes
通常从自己的错误中学习
different subject that you'll find me
找到我的不同主题
talking about a lot is the notion of
谈论很多是
latency and response time how its
延迟和响应时间如何
measured how it behaves you can find a
测量它的行为，你可以找到一个
bunch of stuff online with me talking
一堆东​​西在网上和我聊天
about that and to do one more little
关于这个，再做一点
raise-your-hand survey at the beginning
在开始时进行手工调查
I'd like you to kind of start raising it
我希望您能开始提高它
and keeping them up as I get to a number
并跟着我保持联系
that you recognize or sorry raise them
你认识或后悔抚养他们
drop them laughter how many of you use
放下他们的笑声你们有多少人在用
Java with heaps that are half a gigabyte
Java的堆大小为半GB
or more okay let's first of the room the
还是更好，让我们先进入房间
rest of you are really tiny now
你们其余的人现在真的很小
how many have more than the gigabyte
有多少人超过了千兆字节
keep your hands up if not drop them on
如果不放手，请保持双手举起
about more than two gigabytes more than
大约超过2 GB
four gigabytes more than 10 gigabytes
4 GB超过10 GB
more than 20 50 hundred can't want to
超过20 50万不想
talk to you afterwards now but the
现在再和你说话，但是
reality is any of these let me show you
现实是这些让我告诉你
a magic trick I was guessing that this
我猜这是一个魔术
is where we're gonna group this guess
是我们要把这个猜测分组的地方
has been correct in the last ten years
在过去十年中是正确的
I've been doing talks around this for
我一直在为此进行讨论
about ten years and that hasn't majority
大约十年了，并不是大多数
of this row the drop the hands it
这排放手
that's an interesting observation about
这是一个有趣的观察
the fact that we don't actually make use
我们实际上没有利用的事实
of memory and growth of memory and the
的记忆和记忆的增长
fact that in the last decade we actually
事实上，在过去的十年中，我们实际上
got 100 times the memory for the same
拥有相同内存的100倍
price but we still get the sizes the
价格，但我们仍然可以得到
same that's a big observation and a huge
同样，这是一个很大的发现，一个巨大的发现
reason for them
他们的理由
okay so background why should you know
好吧，背景为什么你应该知道
how garbage collectors work not just how
垃圾收集器的工作方式不只是如何
to tune them and what flags to use why
调整它们以及使用什么标记
should you know a little bit about words
你是否应该对单词有所了解
I like to use practical stories this
我喜欢用实际的故事
actually happened to me then call it the
实际上发生在我身上，然后称之为
story of the good little architect any
好小建筑师的故事
Mark Twain fancier and I define a good
马克·吐温（Mark Twain）鸽友，我定义了一个很好的
architect not by the quality of the
建筑师不是靠质量
architecture but their but their ability
建筑，但他们的能力
to actually make people build an
真正使人们建立一个
architecture if you come up with the
建筑，如果你想出
best beautiful architecture you can
可以的最好的美丽建筑
think of but nobody actually adheres to
想起但没有人真正坚持
it you're not an architect you're a
你不是建筑师，你是一个
philosopher
哲学家
the architects actually get people who
建筑师实际上得到了
build their stuff or at least the
建立自己的东西或至少
successful ones and early in our career
成功者和我们职业生涯的早期
was spotless garbage collector we
是一尘不染的垃圾收集器，我们
actually ran into their success
真正成功了
architect and along with them and ran
建筑师，并与他们一起奔跑
into an 18-second pause and a pause this
停顿18秒，然后停顿一下
collector which was very embarrassing
收藏家很尴尬
this was back in 2006 or so so we went
那是在2006年左右，所以我们去了
in to see what's going on here and when
看看这里发生了什么事，什么时候
we dug into the application to see
我们进入应用程序以查看
what's going on
这是怎么回事
we found some surprising behavior this
我们发现了一些令人惊讶的行为
application had behavior that we
应用程序具有我们的行为
normally didn't see and every time we
通常没有看到，每次我们
did a garbage collection we found that
做一个垃圾收集，我们发现
we had to execute tens of millions of
我们不得不执行数千万
finalizes every time which at least that
最终确定每次至少
the time is very abnormal no because it
时间很不正常，不是因为
was abnormal we didn't bother to make
很不正常，我们没有打扰
that a concurrent operation at the time
当时的并发操作
since then we fix that so now even this
从那以后我们就解决了
won't cause but it was curious we're
不会造成，但很好奇我们
trying to figure out where this comes
试图弄清楚这在哪里
from because we just don't see that
因为我们只是没有看到
normally so we dug into the application
通常，所以我们进入应用程序
with the customer we found out that
与客户我们发现
every single class written in a project
项目中编写的每个类
that ran for about 18 months over ten
过去十个月运行了大约18个月
people how to find one every single
人们如何找到一个单身
class that this team wrote had a
这个团队写的课有一个
finalizer there was a very good
终结者有一个非常好的
architect that playing in here
在这里玩的建筑师
nobody got away from doing this but more
没有人逃避此事，但更多
interesting was what did the finalizes
有趣的是完成了什么
do anybody want to guess what the final
有人想猜最后
residue exactly so the nothing the the
残留物就是这样
final answers were putting nulls in all
最终的答案是将所有内容都设为空
the references to help the collector out
帮助收藏家的参考
because you don't want to if this object
因为你不想如果这个对象
cars you don't want to keep references
您不想保留参考的汽车
to other objects right let's help the
对其他物体，让我们来帮助
collector out by putting those
通过把那些收集出去
everywhere well this is the worst
到处都好，这是最糟糕的
possible thing you can ask a collector
你可能会问收藏家
to do it doesn't help it it hurts it but
这样做无济于事，但是
there is a world where this is exactly
有一个世界，这正是
the right thing to do in C++ this is how
在C ++中要做的正确的事情是这样的
do you write set code you have
你写你的设置代码吗
destructors what are the equivalents you
毁灭者相当于你什么
make sure that if you die you you kill
确保如果你死了就杀了
everything you touch so rough
你碰的一切都那么粗糙
scanning will collect those two and
扫描将收集这两个
whatever else you doing and if you
你还在做什么，如果你
actually don't adhere to this kind of
实际上不坚持这种
architecture you're gonna have memory
您将拥有记忆的架构
leaks and corruptions and all kinds of
泄漏和腐败以及各种
other bad things happening
其他不好的事情正在发生
so you need the structures and
所以你需要的结构和
everything is equal suppose in Java you
一切都是平等的，假设您在Java中
never want destructors or finalizer
从不想要析构函数或终结器
unless you absolutely can't get away
除非你绝对无法摆脱
from doing and even then it should think
从做，甚至它应该认为
three times before so this is the wrong
三遍，所以这是错误的
thing for Java or any garbage collected
Java或任何垃圾收集的东西
language and it's the right thing for
语言，这是正确的
reference counted languages with
参考计数语言
disrupted wine because collectors work
酒被破坏，因为收藏家的工作
in certain ways and we'll get into that
以某些方式，我们将进入
hopefully become evident why this is a
希望能证明这是为什么
such a bad practice it's like a thousand
这么糟糕的做法，就像一千
exports more expensive for the collector
出口使收集者更昂贵
video okay so up being this a little
视频还好吧，这有点
more in general I find that there are a
一般来说，我发现有一个
lot of myths and misunderstandings about
关于许多误解和误解
collection a lot of what people think
收集了很多人的想法
about collection garbage collection is
关于收集垃圾收集是
wrong and most of the advice you will
错误的，大多数建议你会
find an intern that is the opposite of
找到一个与之相反的实习生
correct so even when you read my stuff
正确，所以即使你读我的东西
you should be suspected it but academic
你应该怀疑它，但学术
work tends to be pretty good peer
工作往往是相当不错的同行
reviewed academic papers tend to be
评论的学术论文往往是
pretty good but general internet advice
不错，但是一般的互联网建议
tend to be terrible especially three
往往很糟糕，尤其是三个
years after it was written so and Google
这么多年后，谷歌
doesn't forget so here are some basic
不会忘记，所以这里有一些基本
things there are different than what you
那里的事情不同于你
might think so for example Bob
可能会这样想，例如鲍勃
description isn't a lot better than what
描述并不比什么更好
people think at a few things for example
人们以为有几件事
garbage collection is actually the most
垃圾收集实际上是最
efficient possible way of managing
高效可行的管理方式
memory it is cheaper than any other
内存比其他任何便宜
alternative when it comes to cycles
周期选择
spent for allocation and removal of
用于分配和删除
dynamic things
动态的东西
GC is cheaper than mono period and we
GC比mono便宜，我们
can prove that I'll get into a proof
可以证明我会证明
later
后来
I know no this is controversial that's
我不知道这是有争议的
fine
精细
the other one is the garbage collector
另一个是垃圾收集器
basically doesn't spend an efficient
基本上没有花高效率
carbon script doesn't spend enough any
碳脚本的花费不足
actual work looking and thinking about
寻找和思考的实际工作
that object
该对象
which is why asking to finalize objects
这就是为什么要求完成对象
as a terrible thing because you're
是一件可怕的事情，因为你
asking you to take something that costs
要求你花一些钱
it nothing and actually do an operation
它什么也没有做，实际上是在做手术
for object and then the last part is the
对于对象，然后最后一部分是
garbage collectors at least in Java and
至少在Java和
most modern runtimes
最现代的运行时
will absolutely find all the dead
绝对会找到所有死者
objects they don't need help they don't
他们不需要的物体，他们不需要帮助
need you to break cycles they don't you
需要你打破周期，他们不是你
don't have to worry about linked lists
不必担心链接列表
that point to themselves and weird
指向自己和怪异
graphs of objects if it's dead it's dead
对象图如果死了就死了
you don't need to worry about it they do
您不必担心，他们会
a perfect job
完美的工作
a precise job of finding the dead
寻找死者的精确工作
objects and helping it out there putting
对象并帮助它放在那里
knobs it's just getting in its way
旋钮只是阻碍
doesn't make it more correct it makes it
并没有使它更正确
more stuff but there are a lot of things
更多的东西，但有很多东西
that are worse than what people might
比人们可能会更糟
think for example if you're garbage
想想如果你很垃圾
collector has any form of stopped the
收集器有任何形式的停止
world operation to perform its work I
世界行动，以履行其职责我
can all work out if it's rare or not it
难得都可以解决
will pause for something in the order of
将按以下顺序暂停
a second for gigabyte of my stuff that
一秒钟我的东西
you have you can't get away from that
你有你无法摆脱的
you can delay and yes there are some
您可以延迟，是的，有一些
collectors which will actually not do
收集者实际上不会这样做
that thing is one example there's others
那件事是一个例子，还有其他
in the works but phenom and me if you're
在作品中，但phenom和我，如果你是
doing compaction and stop the world you
做压实，停止世界你
will see the spawns you cannot get away
会看到你无法摆脱的产卵
from it I don't care what other people
从这里我不在乎其他人
tell you now you might be able to get
告诉你现在也许可以
away for it for an hour or a day or a
花一个小时或一天或一个
week but it is there it's just Swift
周，但在那里，就在斯威夫特
over the road beyond that not all memory
超越那条路，不是所有的记忆
leaks the severe winds and garbage
泄漏大风和垃圾
collectors we take care of a lot of
收藏家，我们照顾很多
memory leaks that are common mistake
常见的错误是内存泄漏
bugs that happen in other environments
在其他环境中发生的错误
but fundamental leaks are forgetting to
但是基本的泄漏正在忘记
forget we're still there if you just
忘记了，如果你只是我们仍然在那里
keep accumulating stuff it's going to
不断积累东西
grow it's not a magic point the last one
成长不是最后一个魔术点
here is very important to stability
这对稳定非常重要
garbage collection things to work in the
垃圾收集的东西在
opposite direction of what people want
人们想要的相反方向
from testable systems most of our tuning
来自可测试系统的大部分调整
and garbage character garbage collectors
和垃圾字符垃圾收集器
has been focused on pushing bad problems
一直专注于解决严重问题
to the future making them more and more
未来使它们越来越多
rare not eliminating them but pushing
难得的是不消除它们，而是推动
them forward and that
他们前进，那个
means that when you've tuned your system
意味着当您调整系统后
to finally pass a 20-minute stress test
最终通过了20分钟的压力测试
you haven't actually gotten rid of any
你实际上并没有摆脱任何
problems you've just moved them to
您刚刚将问题移至
minute 21 free QA this is a terrible
第21分钟免费质量检查，这太糟糕了
thing because a well-tuned GC system
之所以这样，是因为一个经过良好调整的GC系统
often takes days or weeks to actually
通常需要几天或几周才能真正
test which is why are some interesting
测试这是为什么有些有趣
tools that help you cause the bad GC
帮助您造成不良GC的工具
things to happen while you run like the
像跑步一样发生的事情
interesting names
有趣的名字
okay let's talk terminology basic
好吧，让我们谈谈基本的术语
terminology starts with classifying the
术语始于对
collectors and how many of you know what
收藏家，你们当中有多少人知道
a pair of garbage collector is okay
一对垃圾收集器还可以
bunch of you how many of you know what a
你们当中有多少人知道
concurrent garbage collectors now this
现在并发垃圾收集器
that is fewer than apparel there's a
比服装少
reason those two words are synonymous in
为什么这两个词在
English there are some languages I grew
英语我成长了一些语言
up speaking Hebrew where there's only
讲希伯来语的地方
one word for both of these but in
这些都一个字，但在
garbage collection classification
垃圾收集分类
they're orthogonal they don't mean the
他们是正交的，这并不意味着
same thing they can create garbage
他们可以制造垃圾的同一件事
collector does its work while your
收集者在您的工作
application is running the garbage
应用程序正在运行垃圾
collector and your applications are
收集器和您的应用程序是
concurrent with each other we often call
我们经常互相称呼
you guys the mutaters you're mutating
你们你们正在变异的变异者
the heap you're changing its shape a
您正在改变其形状的堆
parallel garbage collector is a
并行垃圾收集器是一个
collector that uses more than one thread
使用多个线程的收集器
intimates junk it can use more than one
亲密垃圾，它可以使用多个
thread more than one CPU to do whatever
线程多个CPU做任何事情
it is doing these things have nothing to
它正在做这些事情没有什么可做的
do with each other
互相做
you could be concurrent but not pal you
你可能是并发的，但不是好朋友
could be power but nothing current you
可能是力量，但没有电流
could be neither you could be both these
可能两者都不是
are just definitions of terms
只是术语的定义
unfortunately if you read maybe 30 years
不幸的是，如果您阅读了30年
back in garbage Millington papers you'll
回到垃圾密林顿文件，你会
find these terms actually interchanged
发现这些术语实际上互换了
what used to be called peril is nothing
曾经被称为危险的东西
called concurrent but this is probably
称为并发，但这可能是
good for the last 20 25 years of
对过去的20 25年有利
academic work at least and garbage
至少学术工作和垃圾
collectors so keep in mind that prowling
收藏家，所以要记住
collected current are very different
收集电流有很大不同
things now what does this stop the world
现在的事情是什么阻止了世界
collector will stop the world is the
收藏家将制止世界
opposite of concurrent rather than run
与并发相反，而不是运行
concurrently with your application it
与您的应用程序同时进行
stops the world
停止世界
in advance and then you get to run later
提前，然后再运行
so these are direct opposites a
所以这些是直接相反的
monolithic collector or a part of a
单片收集器或一部分
collector this model I think is that
收藏家我认为这个模式是
that's all the work in one chunk and one
一站式完成所有工作
piece of work that you cannot break into
你无法从事的工作
pieces and maybe do in pieces and run in
碎，也许碎，然后磨合
the middle so long as an incremental
中间只要增量
collector is a collector that can take
收藏家是可以接受的收藏家
the work you need to do shrink it into
您需要做的工作将其缩小为
smaller pieces do a little bit of it
较小的部分可以做到这一点
maybe stop the world do a little bit of
也许停止世界做一点
it then stop stopping the world but you
然后它停止停止世界，但是你
run then do the next journey the next
跑然后做下一个旅程下一个
you might say interleaving its work with
您可能会说与之交织
the application but not concurrently it
应用程序，但不能同时使用
stops you does a little you run
阻止你做一点跑步
something it doesn't do intervening
它不会干预的事情
incremental collectors are usually stop
增量收集器通常会停止
the world incremental runners but
世界增量跑步者，但
there's one very important technical
有一项非常重要的技术
word in garbage collector classification
垃圾收集器分类中的单词
and it is used honestly in academic
它被诚实地用于学术界
terms mostly but it's been kind of abuse
大部分是术语，但这是一种滥用
from a marketing perspective that is the
从营销角度来看，
simple English word mostly mostly means
简单的英语单词主要是指
exactly what you think it means but you
确实是您认为的意思，但您
need to carefully carefully read any
需要仔细仔细阅读任何
sentence that has the word mostly in it
大部分带有单词的句子
mostly concurrent means sometimes
多数情况下并发表示
thought to cram mostly parallel means
被认为以平行方式补习
sometimes single thread and mostly
有时是单线程，大部分是
incremental means sometimes monolithic
增量意味着有时是整体的
mostly it's usually what you put in
通常是你放的东西
front of a really nice thing to say I'm
说我很高兴的话
not doing that or anything I mostly do
不这样做或我通常做的任何事情
that but I was honest with you I said
那但我对你说实话
mostly you'll find that in a lot of
大多数情况下，您会发现
classifications okay let's talk about a
分类好了，让我们来谈谈
few other terminologies precise and
其他一些精确的术语和
conservative collection ism a precise
保守的收藏是精确的
collector well let's start with
收藏家好，让我们开始
conservative a conservative collector is
保守的收藏家是
a collector that's not quite sure where
一个不确定的收藏家在哪里
all the pointers are it's good to go and
所有的指针都很好，
find junk heap but it's not quite sure
找到垃圾堆，但不确定
where all the pointers to everything are
指向一切的所有指针都在哪里
no some but not all and it needs to it
没有一些，但不是全部，它需要它
as a result be conservative some things
结果有些保守
might be pointers might not be pointers
可能是指针，可能不是指针
I need to deal with that
我需要处理
a precise collector is a collector that
精确的收藏家就是
actually does know when it collects
实际上知道它何时收集
where all the pointers are and this
所有指针都在哪里
difference is very fundamental because
差异非常根本，因为
there are some things you cannot do
有些事情你做不到
unless you precise
除非你精确
for example the collector he has to be
例如他必须成为的收藏家
precise if it's gonna move a knob to get
精确，如果要移动旋钮
from one place to another if you move
从一个地方到另一个地方
one object point A to point B you have
一个物体点A到点B
to fix all the pointers to point to it
修复所有指向它的指针
but what if you're not sure where they
但是如果您不确定他们在哪里
are maybe you left one dangling or maybe
也许你留下了一个悬空，或者
worse here's something that I think
更糟糕的是，我认为
might be a pointer but I'm not actually
可能是一个指针，但我实际上不是
sure if it's a pointer an integer maybe
确定它是否是一个整数指针
it's just an integer that happens to
它只是一个整数
have the value that looks like a pointer
具有看起来像指针的值
I'll change my integer value because an
我将更改整数值，因为
object later both of those are deadly
后来反对这两个都是致命的
mistakes to make you can't afford to do
错误使你无力承担
them which is why without being precise
他们，这就是为什么不精确
you will not see any moving objects the
您将看不到任何运动物体
hard work to make the collector precise
努力使收集器精确
is not in the collector itself it's the
不在收藏家本身中
information given by the collector by
收集者提供的信息
the runtime the collector just needs to
收集器只需要在运行时
know where the pointers are but it's
知道指针在哪里，但是
things like the JIT compilers and the
诸如JIT编译器和
runtime that needs to know at any point
任何时候都需要知道的运行时
in code where the collector might
在收集器可能会使用的代码中
collect where all the pointers are for
收集所有指针的位置
example at this point in the stack if I
如果我在堆栈中的这一点上的示例
stopped and collected I need to know all
停下来收集我需要知道所有
the registers if the pointers all the
如果所有的指针
call stacks if they're pointers of that
调用栈，如果它们是该指针
and if I move one code line that changes
如果我移动一条更改的代码行
that information is carried in in
信息随身携带
hotspot on what's called blue perhaps a
所谓的蓝色热点也许是
few other times as well which the
还有其他几次
compilers of the JIT couponers to
JIT优惠券的编译器
produce and next time you need a JIT
生产，下次您需要准时生产
compiler writers think that for doing
编译器作者认为这样做
all that hard work that only it's needed
只需要它的所有辛勤工作
for this kind of stuff because without
对于这种东西，因为没有
it we wouldn't have foresight garbage
它不会有远见的垃圾
collection we wouldn't have compaction
我们不会压实的集合
we would record all the JVM s we have
我们将记录我们拥有的所有JVM
today news precise collectors they all
今天新闻精确的收藏家，他们都
move objects at one point or another
在一个点或另一个点上移动对象
safe points are these interesting things
安全点是这些有趣的事情
that we do in execution to allow these
我们在执行过程中允许这些
for size collectors to work so we could
让尺寸收集器工作，所以我们可以
theoretically have any program counter
理论上有任何程序计数器
point at any point what everything would
在任何时候都指向什么
be but that's both hard and also hurts
是，但这既困难又痛苦
optimization so it is insert safe points
优化，以便插入安全点
in the execution where we say here we
在执行过程中，我们在这里说我们
know where all the pointers are here we
知道所有指针在哪里
know what all the pointers are safe
知道所有指针是安全的
points are ranges of execution in the
点是执行范围
thread where we have full description of
我们完整描述的线程
what the pointers are amount of stuff
指针是什么东西
between them we may not but there we do
他们之间我们可能不会，但我们在那里
there are all kinds of safe points and
有各种各样的安全点，
GCC point and safe point I'm using
我正在使用的GCC点和安全点
interchangeably here there are other
可互换的这里还有其他
reasons for safe points as well when I
当我安全点的原因
say that we bring a thread through a
说我们通过一个线程
safe point it means that we get it to
安全点，这意味着我们可以做到
that range of execution that we have a
我们拥有的执行范围
good description for and don't let it go
很好的描述，不要放过
past that point and that sounds a lot
超过这一点，这听起来很多
like stumping the thread right and
像树桩一样，
stopping this event is one way to do
停止此事件是一种方法
that there's one key exception to it
有一个关键的例外
for example J Michaels anytime you call
例如您随时致电J Michaels
j9 function including blocking a socket
j9功能包括阻止套接字
or a read or anything else anything you
或阅读或其他任何东西
actually enter a safe point now entering
实际上进入一个安全点，现在进入
the safe one doesn't mean you're not
安全的人并不意味着你不是
running you could be inverting a matrix
运行，您可能正在反转矩阵
in C++ for the next three hours but you
在接下来的三个小时中使用C ++，但是您
are not changing any pointer states
没有改变任何指针状态
you're not changing where the pointers
你没有改变指针的位置
are so you are at a signal we have a
所以你是一个信号，我们有一个
good description for where do we need
我们需要在哪里的好描述
safe place to be frequent otherwise
否则经常去的安全地方
we'll have what I call it time to safe
我们将拥有我所说的安全时间
white problem not gonna get into it here
白色的问题不在这里
but it's fundamental either you know
但这很重要
everybody's waiting and this one guy
每个人都在等待，这个家伙
hasn't come back for the last three
最近三天没回来
hours
小时
looks like a big pause but nothing has
看起来像是一个很大的停顿，但什么也没有
started working it but there is a local
开始工作，但有一个本地
safe point where we bring all the
安全点，我们将所有
threads to a common safe point and that
线程到一个共同的安全点，那
is what is known as they stop the world
是他们阻止世界的方式
pause the global safe point and stop
暂停全局安全点并停止
with what laws are the same thing
与什么法律是同一回事
so we talked about some terms let's talk
所以我们讨论了一些术语
about some behaviors here are the three
关于一些行为，这是三个
things that all precise collectors in
所有精确的收藏家都喜欢的东西
the practical term will do one of them
实际条件会做其中之一
is they will identify all the live
他们会识别所有现场
objects that there are they will reclaim
他们将回收的物体
all that
所有的
that they can prove are dead and they
他们可以证明已经死了，他们
will relocate objects from one place to
将物体从一个地方移到
another every one of these things will
这些东西中的每一个都会
happen in a precise collector there's no
发生在一个精确的收集器中，没有
real point in being precise if you don't
如果你不做的话，准确就是要点
do all three but let's look at concrete
完成这三个步骤，但让我们看一下具体的
examples and classic simple algorithms
示例和经典的简单算法
that do these steps the first one is a
做这些步骤的第一个是
mark sweep compact collector
打标机
marking is where you find all the line
标记是找到所有线的地方
object that's step one sweeping is where
第一步的对象是
you identify all the dead stuff and
您确定所有死者的东西，
somehow the only three cycling it that's
不知何故，只有三个循环
step two and then compacted step three
第二步，然后压实第三步
one two three one two three but
一二三一二三但是
separately there's a separate command
分别有一个单独的命令
collector called the copy collector
收集器称为副本收集器
which doesn't do this as three steps a
这不是三个步骤
copy collector from the maddening takes
从疯狂的副本收集器
all the objects from one space and call
所有物体都来自一个空间并调用
it from space say let's move all the
从太空说，让我们移动所有
live stuff to a two space in one pass
一站式将活物带到两个空间
and when I'm done and the other that all
当我完成后，其他的一切
the stuff is in the two space so from
东西在两个空间中，所以从
space is empty
空间是空的
that's a single pass that does all three
这是一次通过所有三个步骤
of these things find the objects move
这些东西发现物体移动
them and as a result every claim to
他们，因此每个要求
business so I'm going to break that on
业务，所以我要打破它
the actual faces of the ones I just
我只是那些人的真实面孔
talked about as explanation so we can
谈论作为解释，所以我们可以
talk about them in complexity marking or
在复杂性标记中谈论它们或
tracing it involves starting from what
跟踪涉及从什么开始
we call roots roots are static variables
我们称根根是静态变量
the threads and their stacks themselves
线程及其堆栈本身
things that are the roots of visibility
可见性的根源
pointers I can start from and we start
我可以从那里开始的指针，我们开始
from these groups we do what we call
从这些群体中我们做我们所谓的
tracing or painting anything they can
追踪或绘画任何他们可以
reach that does not get them marked I
达到并没有将它们标记为I
reach I mark and then they look inside
到达我标记，然后他们看向里面
of it and keep reaching so I let the
它，并不断达到，所以我让
paint and follow everything I could see
绘画并遵循我所看到的一切
and everywhere I go I mark that I've
在我走过的任何地方，我都标记为
been there if I get to a place that
我去过那里
already marked that they need to go
已经标记为他们需要走
there again so I start from the roots
再次出现，所以我从根开始
and actually I can reach in now at the
实际上我现在可以到达
end of one of these exhausts of tracing
这些追踪的精髓之一的结尾
passes that starts from the roots all
从根开始的通行证
the reachable objects anything they can
可以到达的物体
reach you from my root set is going to
从我的根本出发到达你
be marked line
被标记为线
and anything I can't reach from the
还有我无法到达的任何东西
roots I will not be worth like there's a
根源，我将不值得拥有
very important quality here if I cannot
如果不能的话，这里非常重要的品质
reach it from the root set now I will
现在从根目录到达它
never be able to reach it from the root
永远无法从根源到达它
set again to be able to express a
再次设置以能够表达
reference to an object I need to be able
引用我需要的对象
to reach it before an expressive so the
在表达之前达到它，所以
copying the reference rather it's only
复制参考，而仅仅是
reachable thing
可触及的东西
so once I've shown that something isn't
所以一旦我证明有些东西不是
reachable it is there it's not becoming
可以到达的地方
alive again this is why a circular
这又是为什么还活着
linked list doesn't have to be tagged
链接列表不必标记
and broken because if I can't reach into
和破碎，因为如果我无法达到
it it's gonna be dead doesn't have to
它会死的，不必
break things apart
分开
so that's tracing it's exhaustive but
所以这是详尽无遗的
from the complexity point of view it's
从复杂性的角度来看
work grows with the live set with the
工作随着现场的发展而增长
men of live objects and like references
活物和类似参考文献的人
we have to move through but that with
我们必须经历，但是
the size of the heat if I have a twenty
如果我有二十的话，热量的大小
gigabyte heat for a hundred feet up I
千兆字节的热量高达一百英尺
keep and only have a hundred megabyte of
保持只有100兆字节的
live stuff I'm only marking 100 megabyte
活东西，我只标记100兆字节
of live stuff the size of the heap has
堆大小的活东西
nothing to do with the complexity of the
与复杂性无关
market but if I double the life set it
市场，但如果我把生活加倍
will grow to swing here to myself
会变身到我这里
sweeping is a very simple mechanism
清扫是一个非常简单的机制
imagine I just did a mark and everything
想象我只是做了一个记号，一切
that's alive is alive and if not is not
那还活着就是活着，如果不是，那不是
we sweep through the whole team looking
我们席卷整个团队
at all the objects and if they're not
在所有物体上，如果不是
live we somehow deal with them recycling
生活中，我们以某种方式处理它们的回收
them every second later putting them in
他们每秒钟将它们放入
freeness is one common way to go through
自由是一种通行的方式
everything everything that's that put in
一切都放进去
our fingers we'll deal with it later
我们的手指，我们稍后会处理
this is obviously a simple pass we can
这显然是我们可以通过的简单通行证
paralyze it or not but it's work is
瘫痪与否，但它的工作是
linear to the size of the heap but after
与堆大小成线性关系，但之后
you manage and visit every single object
您管理和访问每个对象
regardless of events that are alive if I
无论我活着的事件如何
double the heap size I double the work
将堆大小加倍我将工作加倍
changing the lights that has no
改变没有的灯
effective in the work like not
在工作中很有效
significant leaders okay so once we've
重要的领导人好吧，所以一旦我们
marked and swept
标记并扫过
we know where all the good stuff is we
我们知道所有好东西都在哪里
have compact this is a simple mark sweet
紧凑，这是一个简单的标记，甜蜜
completo
补全
let's start with why do we need to
让我们开始，为什么我们需要
compact people often argue about this
紧凑的人经常为此争论
but I think the arguments are so
但我认为争论是如此
probably twenty years ago or more the
大概二十年前或更早
reason we compact is because if you
我们紧凑的原因是，如果您
don't over time your heap will get Swiss
不要随着时间的流逝你的堆会变得瑞士
cheese you'll end up with halls
奶酪，你会以大厅结束
everywhere and even though the heap is
到处都是，即使堆是
90% empty you have no place to put your
90％为空，您无处可放
11 kilobyte string because the biggest
11 KB的字符串，因为最大
Hall is nine kilobytes there's 100
大厅是9千字节，那里有100
gigabytes of free memory but not whole
GB的可用内存，但不是全部
big enough in your 11 of your library
在您的11个图书馆中足够大
and that would be very embarrassing if
如果这会很尴尬
we threw an out of memory exception at
我们在以下位置抛出了内存不足异常
that point so because of that we have to
那一点，因此，我们必须
compact now the reality is in the real
现在紧凑，现实是真实的
world when you have variable size
大小可变时的世界
objects with variable mixes of size
大小可变的对象
going over time you will threaten them
随着时间的流逝，您将威胁他们
to heat it's unavoidable there's no real
加热是不可避免的，没有真正的
argument about this in the term it's
关于这个的争论是
just a question of how long can you live
只是你能活多久的问题
before you have to do this that has a
在您必须执行此操作之前
lot of or variations but anyway we will
很多或变化，但无论如何我们都会
need to compact so what this compacting
需要压实，所以这种压实
me what compacting means moving objects
我压实意味着移动物体
together to make bigger halls and there
一起做更大的大厅
are various - thanks for doing that for
种类繁多-感谢您这样做
example you can compact in place which
例如，您可以将其压缩到位
is what the marks we compact collected
是我们紧紧收集的标记
in topology see does which is think of
在拓扑中看到的是什么想到的
it as we marked everything respect
当我们标记一切尊重时
everything move all the life stuff to
一切都将所有生命的东西转移到
the left
左边
that's compacting it to the left then
然后将其压缩到左侧
I'll have all the empty stuff on the
我将所有空的东西放在上面
right it'll be configures so we
正确，它将进行配置，所以我们
basically are gonna move stuff together
基本上会一起搬东西
to get all the empty stuff to be big and
让所有空的东西变大
it basically has to then not just move
它基本上必须不只是移动
the objects but we move the objects they
物体，但我们移动物体
have to fix all the pointers to those
必须修复所有指向这些指针的指针
objects so we get us some attract them
对象，所以我们让我们吸引一些对象
and pass and fix them
并通过并修复它们
that's a compacted place there are
那是一个紧凑的地方
evacuation compactors that take and take
疏散压实机
a region of memory and move all the live
一个记忆区域，并移动所有活动
stuff out of it and now the region is
里面的东西，现在该地区是
empty the similar technique from marking
从标记中清空类似的技术
and fixing up the references - but it's
并修正参考文献-但这是
not the difference in behaviour the fix
不是行为上的差异
the point is very important if I moved
如果我搬家，这点很重要
one object that object might have a
一个对象可能具有一个对象
billion things pointing to it so I have
十亿东西指向它，所以我有
to scan the heap for every possible
扫描堆中所有可能的东西
pointer to this object and fix it why we
指向此对象并修复它的原因
never ever move
永不动
because that would be very inefficient
因为那将是非常低效的
so we tend to move a lot of objects
所以我们倾向于移动很多物体
together or most of the objects together
在一起或大多数对象在一起
because then we get to do one pass to
因为这样我们就可以通过
fix everything up together complexity
解决所有问题的复杂性
wise even though this is a pretty bad in
明智的做法，即使这在
heavy operation it's only linear to the
繁重的操作仅与
life so that we have to move the live
生活，所以我们必须搬家
objects and only give to fix the line
对象，只给修复线
references so the heap size doesn't
引用，因此堆大小不
really change the work yet bring the
真正改变了工作却带来了
light side absolutely okay
光的一面绝对可以
the other type of collector I talked
我说过的另一种收藏家
about a coffee collector this one takes
关于一个咖啡收集器，这需要
objects from the front space and moves
来自前方空间的物体并移动
them to through space starting from the
他们从
roots moving everything you can find
扎根移动您可以找到的一切
puts it in a new space and at the end we
放在一个新的空间，最后我们
have an empty from space it's actually
实际上是空的
very effective very efficient it's a
非常有效非常有效
single pass linear moving to the life
单程线性移动到生活
side and is actually a very common news
方面，实际上是一个非常普遍的新闻
collection for some mechanisms however a
一些机制的收集
thing to keep in mind here is it needs a
这里要记住的事情是它需要一个
to space in the to space in a simple
在一个简单的空间
without thinking other things happen
没想到其他事情会发生
around it collector needs to be as big
周围的收集器需要一样大
as the from space because we don't know
作为太空，因为我们不知道
every anything is that we might have to
每件事都是我们可能必须
move everything and this is usually
移动一切，这通常是
monolithic you start to move everything
整体式，您开始移动一切
you can't believe anything behind so the
你不敢相信任何东西，所以
to space needs to have room for all my
空间需要我所有的空间
stuff which is as big as current heat
与目前的热量一样大的东西
because I don't know how much is that in
因为我不知道那是多少
there that's the simple so looking at
就是这么简单，所以看着
some of the qualities copying requires
一些质量复制要求
2x because of what I just said a mark
因为我刚才说的标记是2倍
compact without the sweeping an
紧凑而不扫地
evacuating more compact my 8 2 X the
疏散我的8 2 X
memory to do a full compaction but it
进行完全压缩的内存，但是
could stop in the middle because it's
可能会停在中间，因为
doing the region at a time a mark sweep
一次打扫区域
contact with compacted place doesn't
接触压实的地方不
need extra memory to compact that's a
需要额外的内存来压缩，这是一个
nice bus both the coffee and mark
咖啡和马克都不错的公共汽车
compact are linear only to the amount of
紧致仅线性于量
live stuff it's the sweet that grows
活的东西，是增长的甜蜜
with the heat mic sweep impact
与热麦克风扫击
and is linear also to the heap and then
并且对堆也是线性的，然后
mark-sweep and sometimes compact I
打标，有时紧凑I
didn't talk much about but that's a
没有太多谈论，但这是一个
common attempted to be related to the
常见的试图与
vegan then I talked about the monolithic
素食主义者然后我谈论了整体
part of company let's talk about
公司的一部分，让我们谈谈
generational collection that brings some
分代收集带来一些
of these things together I talked about
我一起谈论这些事情
the efficiency in the linearity of these
这些线性的效率
algorithms for a reason generational
原因生成算法
collection is a really cool thing that
收藏是一件很酷的事情
was introduced to the 1984 based on this
在此基础上引入1984年
observation
观察
it's called weak generational hypothesis
这就是所谓的弱代假设
and if it's most optimist objects that
如果是最乐观的对象
young means soon after I look it's that
年轻的意思是我看后不久
most of stuff out of people dying that
大多数人死于那种
don't equate this with most life objects
不要等同于大多数生命对象
are most life objects I think them to be
是我认为大多数生活对象
all they're the ones who survived but
他们都是幸存下来的人，
dynamically out of every ten objects I
动态地每十个对象我
look at nine dollars that's a very
看九美元，这是非常
strong observation it's usually more
强烈的观察通常会更多
than that to work knowing that this is
比知道这是工作
true or believing that this is true we
真实或相信这是真实的，我们
can apply what we talked about in
可以运用我们在
efficiencies to make a very efficient
提高效率的效率
generational collector when we do that
当我们这样做的世代收藏家
as we focus on weak on what we call the
当我们专注于所谓的弱点
young generation the region of the
年轻一代的地区
memory that was recently allocated
最近分配的内存
believing that the vast majority of this
相信绝大多数
is that the vast majority is that means
是绝大多数的意思是
the life set is a very small percentage
寿命设定的比例很小
of the heap size so I want to pick an
堆大小，所以我想选择一个
algorithm that's linear only to the live
仅与实时线性相关的算法
set and not to the heap size and there
设置而不是堆大小
won't be an efficiency as long as they
只要他们有效率
were of similar size you know 2x here or
大小相似，您在这里知道2倍，或者
something but if I think that only 1% or
但如果我认为只有1％或
0.1% is alive and I apply a copy
0.1％还活着，我申请了一份副本
collector to that that's a hundred times
那个收藏家的一百倍
more efficient to the sleeping
睡觉更有效率
collectors if this stuff is dead how do
收藏家如果这东西死了怎么办
we keep the stuff true how do we make
我们保持真实，我们如何做
sure that this assumption remains true
确保这个假设是正确的
things do survive and if we keep them in
事情确实存在，如果我们坚持下去
this thing they'll keep accumulating and
他们会不断积累的东西，
this sparseness will stop being true so
这种稀疏将不再是真的，所以
things that have been around for a while
已经存在了一段时间的事情
we have to put somewhere else
我们必须放在其他地方
we need the young generation to be done
我们需要年轻一代去做
because this assumption is true about
因为这个假设是正确的
young stuff and that's what promotion is
年轻的东西，那就是晋升
stuff that has been around long enough
已经存在了足够长的时间
somewhere else so we keep being
在其他地方，所以我们一直在
efficient in their generation now there
现在那里的一代人
are places where I've seen people tweak
在我见过人们调整的地方
the young generation too you know with
你也认识的年轻一代
size and promotion thresholds to never
规模和晋升门槛从未达到
promote to try really really hard to not
促进尝试真的很难
promote all they're doing is making a
促进他们正在做的所有事情就是
single generational collector where
单代收藏家在哪里
there's no weak generational offenses
没有弱小的世代相传
and all the efficiency is out the window
而所有的效率都在窗外
you have to get rid of that big spoon
你必须摆脱那把大汤匙
efficiency to be there once we get rid
一旦摆脱，效率就在那里
of them and put them somewhere else we
他们，并把它们放在其他地方
collect events somewhere else the old
在其他地方收集事件
generation when it fills up with
充满时的一代
whatever collector would use for them
任何收藏家会为他们使用
and this tends to be a order of
这往往是一个顺序
magnitude plus filter so today and most
幅度加滤波器，所以今天和大多数时候
workloads are most I mean the vast
我的意思是说工作量最大
majority of workloads every workload I
大部分工作负载
look at a GC long form we're looking at
看我们正在看的GC长格式
a ten to one twenty to one ratio between
两者之间的比例为十比十二
the work we need to do if we have a
如果我们有一个工作，我们需要做的工作
generational collector and if we did it
分代收藏家，如果我们做到了
for the same awkward it's a pretty
同样尴尬的是
effective filter there are few other
有效过滤器很少
things about it to do this magic we need
做这个魔术所需的事情
to maintain something we call me and
维持我们称为我的东西
remember it second we need to know about
记得第二件事，我们需要知道
the routes into the young generation
通往年轻一代的途径
should we can only look at the young
我们只能看看年轻人吗
generation or not at all if we look at
世代相传或根本不相传
the whole team game over so we do that
整个团队比赛都结束了，所以我们做到了
with something that lets us know about
让我们知道的东西
all the pointers from the all to they
从所有人到他们的所有指针
honor their various techniques for that
为此纪念他们的各种技巧
Clarke marking is is one of those and
克拉克标志就是其中之一，
I'll talk about it a little bit the
我会谈一点
other nice thing about generational
关于世代的其他好处
collection is we can use something like
收集是我们可以使用类似
a copying collectively in generation but
一代人集体复制，但
not have 2x the memory in there because
那里没有2倍的内存，因为
if we can't fit there the entire from
如果我们不能容纳整个
space in the first place will just spill
首先的空间只会溢出
it over to Belgium but the young
它到了比利时，但是年轻
generation doesn't have to be twice the
代不一定是两倍
size this is why if you look at hotspot
大小，这就是为什么如果您查看热点
for example the Eden pits to be much
例如伊甸园坑很多
larger survivor spaces it's not that you
更大的幸存者空间不是你
know it's gonna fit there it's just if
知道它会适合那里，只是
it doesn't
它没有
okay so remember it sets are these
好吧，请记住它是这些
important things that we want cover here
我们想要涵盖的重要内容
a little I'll say about them is this in
我会说一些关于他们的事情
order to track all the points from the
为了跟踪所有的点
old generation to the young generation
老一辈到年轻一代
we have to intercept anything that
我们必须拦截任何
stores such a pointer or scan is another
存储这样的指针或扫描是另一个
way that router will be less efficient
路由器效率降低的方式
this is why there's a write barrier in
这就是为什么在
most collectors that are generational
大多数收藏家都是世代相传的
that the tracks all pointer rights so
跟踪所有指针的权限，因此
that it could keep track of the set the
它可以跟踪设置
base assumption is this set is very
基本假设是这个集合非常
small sparse if most of the auction
稀疏，如果大部分拍卖
point into the engine the weeks in the
指向引擎中的几周
original hypothesis is probably wrong to
原始假设可能是错误的
begin with so it tends to be very good
开始，所以它往往是非常好的
at very efficient to work that way and
以这种方式非常有效地工作
card marking which is a technique that's
卡标记是一种技术
used by all the JVM seems to work well
所有JVM都使用它似乎工作良好
now if we put all these things together
现在，如果我们把所有这些东西放在一起
we talked about terms and mechanisms
我们讨论了术语和机制
let's look at how they come together
让我们看看他们如何在一起
into actual collectors the young
成为真正的收藏家的年轻人
generation all the collectors all the
产生所有的收藏家
current production collectors are
当前的生产收藏家是
generational there's some non generation
世代相传
law sacred generational I'm very
法律神圣的世代，我非常
interested in your talk later that
以后对你的演讲感兴趣
explains how you can have to do a
解释了您必须如何做
generation then that are not but in the
那一代不是，但在
production systems this is absolutely
生产系统这绝对是
true the youngster ational the
真正的年轻人
concentration is usually a copying
浓度通常是复制
collector and it's usually a monolithic
收藏家，通常是一个整体
stop the world copying every word on
停止世界复制每个单词
this slide has been defined now and
现在已经定义了这张幻灯片，
these are terms that we talking about
这些是我们谈论的术语
not just words the whole generation is
不只是整个世代的话
usually some form of a mark compact may
通常某种形式的商标契约可能
sweetly not the old generation might be
甜蜜的不是老一辈
stopped the world like the concurrent
像并发一样停止了世界
might be partially concurrent might be
可能是部分并发的
increment will stop the world are all
增量将阻止世界
cast with combinations this is usually
通常结合使用
where a lot of the interesting
那里很多有趣的地方
differences are now if we look beyond
如果我们超越未来，现在是不同的
just those classifications have stopped
只是那些分类停止了
the world and stopped the one would be
世界，并停止了一个将是
simple there are a few known stuff of
很简单，有一些已知的东西
all techniques that have been out there
所有已经存在的技术
for a while for example one if I want to
一会儿，例如，如果我想
mark without stopping the world
标记不停止世界
the g1 collector the CMS collector do
g1收集器，CMS收集器
this one way to do this is to deal with
做到这一点的一种方法是应对
the simple race that happens if you do
如果您这样做，就会发生简单的比赛
it and plug it up the simple race that
并将其插入简单的种族
will happen is if I'm going around
如果我要走的话，将会发生
marking painting everything I can see
标记画我所能看到的一切
and you know the mutator it's picking up
而且你知道变种人正在捡起
an object I haven't looked at yet it
我还没看过的物体
puts a reference to it behind me in a
在我后面提到了它
place I visited and won't visit again
我去过的地方，以后不会再去
then get rid of all the references to it
然后摆脱对它的所有引用
I might not see the object might not
我可能看不到对象
mark it alive might collect it even
标记为活着甚至可以收集它
though it's alive and that would be
虽然还活着，那将是
embarrassing so we have to plug up that
令人尴尬的，所以我们必须塞住
incorrect marking race and there's only
不正确的打标比赛，只有
one real concurrent working race that
一场真正的并发工作竞赛
needs to be plugged up somehow we have
需要以某种方式插入
to prevent that propagation from
防止传播
something that haven't seen to be only
有些东西不只是
to what a visitor one of the common ways
访客常用的方式之一
to do this is with multi pass marquee
要做到这一点是与多遍字幕
idea there is the you you track every
想法有你跟踪的每一个
mutation of every pointer in memory
内存中每个指针的变异
become your right to a pointer you track
成为您跟踪的指针的权利
that and then when you finish your
那然后当你完成你的
concurrent pass you say well that's
并发通行证，你说的很好
probably good but I've missed something
可能不错，但是我错过了一些东西
so let's go and everything let's look at
所以我们走吧，让我们看看一切
everything that mutated and work on that
一切变异的东西
and when you finish looking at all the
当你看完所有
stuff that you've marked as I've touched
您标记为我感动的东西
this maybe you're done but maybe you
这也许你完成了，但也许你
need to do it again when you feel good
感觉良好时需要再次做
about it when you think the list is
当您认为列表是
small you might stop the world and
小，你可能会阻止世界，
finish the work depending an algorithm
根据算法完成工作
you've used you may be able to make this
您已经使用过，也许可以做到这一点
converge provably or not
是否收敛
CMS collected for example just three
CMS仅收集了三个
tries and we'll have some unknown amount
尝试，我们将有一些未知数
of working set of ten but the g1
十个工作集，但g1
collector uses a snapshot at the
收集器使用快照
beginning marker that can prove that
可以证明的开始标记
this converges but these are techniques
这会聚，但这是技巧
that example they involve tracking
该示例涉及跟踪
mutation as you write every right to the
当您将所有权利写入
heat now costs you the other interesting
热量现在使您失去了其他兴趣
thing you could do is try to not compact
你可以做的就是尽量不要紧凑
the entire universe at one time if you
如果您一次将整个宇宙
agree that compaction Rob it and then
同意压实抢它，然后
you try and do incremental compaction
您尝试做增量压缩
this is fundamentally what you want this
这基本上就是你想要的
what does that mean we track the cross
这意味着我们追踪十字架
region stuff
地区的东西
the pointers between regions as a
区域之间的指针作为
different kind of remembrancer and then
不同类型的记忆，然后
we try and find regions that have only a
我们尝试找到只有一个
few other regions pointing to them or
指向他们的其他一些地区或
sets of regions is a point to only a
区域集仅指向一个
small set of regions we compact the
一小部分区域，我们将
target regions knowing that I only need
知道我只需要的目标区域
to fix the pointers in a small set of
将指针固定在一小部分中
regions rather than the Hongki but I
地区而不是弘基，但我
hope I could find those sets this
希望我能找到这些设置
actually works pretty well but it could
实际上效果很好，但是可以
run into degenerate behaviors where you
遇到堕落的行为
end up with a very empty region with a
最后是一个非常空的区域
very popular object in it so you're not
非常受欢迎的物品，所以您不会
going to compact that then you'll do the
将其压缩，然后您将
same for other regions eventually you
最终其他地区也一样
have to compact the tiny bit of the even
必须压缩偶数的微小部分
ligament so those are fundamentally
韧带，所以那些基本上
improvements but they're part of what I
改进，但它们是我的一部分
call the denying the inevitable trend of
称之为否认的必然趋势
garbage collection in general we start
一般我们开始垃圾收集
with some understanding that you can't
有了一些了解，你不能
get away from compaction and then we
摆脱压实，然后我们
basically say let's go after the empty
基本上说让我们去空之后
spaces or the cheaper spaces to get
空间或更便宜的空间来获得
stuff from first and we apply a
从头开始，我们应用
generational collector that's a great
一代代的收藏家很棒
efficiency technique but also reduces
效率技术，但也减少了
pauses for until we have to do the altar
停下来直到我们要做祭坛
but eventually you have to develop so
但最终你必须发展
then you look at the doulton and say
然后你看着道尔顿说
well I don't want to compact that whole
好吧，我不想压缩整个
thing maybe I can avoid compacting it
也许我可以避免将其压缩
maybe I can keep things in free lists
也许我可以把东西放在免费清单上
for a while until I have to compact it
一段时间，直到我不得不将其压缩
that's what CMS does but eventually so
CMS就是这么做的，但最终如此
you look at that compaction to say maybe
你看着那个压实说
I won't have to do it on once maybe I
我不必一次做，也许我
could do it a piece at a time and that's
一次可以做一件，那就是
what she wanted us but eventually you're
她想要我们，但最终你是
gonna have to deal with popular objects
将不得不处理受欢迎的物品
and other pressures only need to come
其他压力只需要出现
out of that if we look at the natural
如果我们看看自然
collectors you deal with today
您今天处理的收藏家
there's the classification I said most
我最常说的分类
of all finder let's look at start with
首先，我们先来看一下
perrault you see LTC is a classic barrel
您看到LTC是经典的桶装
collector has a peril monolithic stop
收集器有危险的整体停止
the world copying agent pretty much
世界复制代理几乎
everything I say it's paralleled by the
我所说的一切都与
way it also has a monolithic stop the
它也有整体停止的方式
world mark sleep compact okay it's
世界标记的睡眠紧凑好吧
pretty much like top
很像顶
it's efficient it's fast stop the world
高效，快速停止世界
for everything it does let's look at the
对于它所做的一切，我们来看一下
CMS concurrent mark-sweep collector
CMS并发标记清除收集器
common collector use for hot sensitive
普通收集器用于热敏
applications what do you guys think the
你们怎么看待
Newton to the young generation collector
牛顿给年轻的收藏家
of the CMS collector classified what
CMS收集器的分类
kind of company
种公司
it's a monolithic stopped the world
这是一个单块的世界
copying collector it's exactly the same
复制收集器是完全一样的
algorithm classification is the parity
算法分类是奇偶校验
see what does that have to do with CMS
看看与CMS有什么关系
well nothing CMS is named for its old
嗯，CMS并没有以其古老的名字命名
generation behavior the young generation
一代人的行为
is a monolithic stop the world collector
是一个整体的世界收藏家
it is not concurrent and it's not March
它不是并发的，也不是三月
the old gen is they mostly concurrent
老一代是他们大多数并发
described so in the academic paper that
在学术论文中如此描述
describes algorithm mostly confer not a
描述算法主要不是
compacting Walton it's got this multi
压实沃尔顿，它有很多
pass marker that's mostly concurrent
通过标记，该标记几乎是并发的
it's got a fully concurrent sleeper
它有一个完全并行的卧铺
keeps things in Sweetman and free lists
将内容保存在Sweetman和免费列表中
and then it has this doesn't compact
然后它有这个不紧凑
part which is where the mostly comes in
这是最主要的部分
because you can't get away from
因为你无法摆脱
compaction so that's what it does when
压缩，所以这就是当
it has to compact it does a monolithic
它必须紧凑它做一个整体
stop the world mark sweet compact CMS
停止世界标记甜蜜紧凑型CMS
apart is a filter between the neutron
除了是中子之间的过滤器
and the fold you see it's an effective
而你看到的折叠是有效的
filter but eventually you'll have to
过滤器，但最终您必须
focus this is a big reason G one exists
关注这是一个存在的重要原因
as a collector because of the
作为收藏家，因为
realization that you can't get out of
意识到你无法摆脱
context so let's look at G 1 what does
上下文，所以让我们看一下G 1是什么
the new gen of G 1 plus minus G 1 is an
G 1加G 1的新代是
incremental garbage first
增量垃圾优先
Lee well it's a monolithic stuff the
李，这是一个整体的东西
world copying collector you know this
世界复制收藏家，你知道这个
Kevin it's all Jen has a mostly
凯文这就是简所有的一切
concurrent marker but it's a much better
并发标记，但这要好得多
mostly than another worker it is
主要是比其他工人
provably
可证明地
it will provably converge so you can't
它会证明收敛，所以您不能
run an application it'll make it run
运行一个应用程序，它将使其运行
forever but it has a stop the world
永远，但是它阻止了世界
mostly incremental convector it does not
主要是增量对流，它不会
compare concurrently it stops the world
同时比较，它停止了世界
for any compaction in the only way it
唯一的压缩方式
frees memory is to compare it so the
释放内存是为了进行比较，因此
only way to reach the memory is to stop
到达内存的唯一方法是停止
the world but it tries to do that in
世界，但它试图做到这一点
small increments well I actually have a
小增量，我实际上有一个
quote here from the objective design
引用目标设计
objective of the collector it says we
说我们的收藏家的目标
try to avoid as much as possible having
尽量避免
a full TC what does it tell you right
完整的TC会告诉您什么
there it has an HEC design by design
那里有按设计的HEC设计
it's the site to have afford you see as
这是您负担得起的网站
a fall out to fall back from trying to
跌倒以试图摆脱
do the right thing with incremental but
用增量做正确的事情，但是
you will end up maybe don't take longer
你最终可能不会花更长的时间
maybe you could use them so for your
也许您可以使用它们，以便您
application it won't happen for a long
应用程序不会持续很长时间
time but by designers a Fugees okay so I
时间，但由设计师Fugees可以，所以我
classified the normal hot spot
分类正常热点
collectors the ones you can use today
收集您今天可以使用的
I'm gonna talk a little about this
我要谈一点
monolithic stop the world's you see
单片停止世界的看到
problem or the stop the world in general
问题或停止整个世界
but there are many ways to deal with
但是有很多方法可以应对
some the world GC this is the most
世界上一些最大的GC
common way so you know you can just go
普通的方式，所以你知道你可以走了
to the other talks to talk about how did
在其他谈话中谈论如何
you fit right imagine that this is not a
您合适吧，想象这不是一个
problem one may be will tune it so it'll
问题之一可能是对其进行调整，以便
run this long without a GC with declare
在没有GC声明的情况下运行了这么长时间
success you know 40 minutes no GC game
成功，您知道40分钟没有GC游戏
but then you look longer and you see
但是你看起来更长一些，你会看到
that they're glitches and you look over
他们是小故障，你看看
days and you see that there are regular
天，你会发现有规律
glitches another way is to use creative
小故障的另一种方法是使用创意
language to to make yourself feel better
使自己感觉更好的语言
about the fact that you have stopped of
关于您已经停止的事实
what you sees that will just freeze your
您所看到的将冻结您的
entire application for no good reason
没有充分的理由整个申请
except for the collector wants the
除了收藏家想要的
convocation
召集
these are actual sentences for marketing
这些是营销的实际句子
material and design goals on the web not
网络上的材料和设计目标
making any of these up this is from an
弥补这些是从
actual marketing material of a GVM I
GVM I的实际营销材料
can't name but I could say that it has
无法命名，但我可以说它有
something to do with determinism in that
与确定性有关
brilliant sentence it said I will
辉煌的一句话说我会
guarantee a worse case of 5 milli second
保证5毫秒的更坏情况
nineteen nine percent of the time
百分之十九的时间
doesn't that sound great it's a
听起来不是很好，这是一个
guarantee I'll just point out that one
保证我会指出
percent of one hour is 36 seconds I'm
一小时的百分比是36秒
allowed to pause for 36 seconds once an
一次可以暂停36秒
hour and I've met my guarantee or 360
小时，我已经达到了保证金或360
milliseconds that's that's a meaningless
毫秒是没有意义的
statement that makes you feel good but
能让您感觉良好的陈述，但
there are others mostly as I said put
正如我所说，主要还有其他人
mostly in front of stuff makes people
大多在东西前面让人
feel them that's what it means right so
感觉到他们的意思就是这样
so that's what it literally means it's
这就是它的字面意思
telling you right there it's honest you
告诉你就对了你很诚实
just want to read it the other way you
只想以另一种方式阅读它
want it you don't want to hear about the
想要它，您不想听到关于
restaurant very consistent I've heard
我听说过的餐厅非常一致
this a lot you know it's a call that's
很多你知道这是一个电话
actually a Jekyll for a future version
实际上是未来版本的Jekyll
of g1 to be fairly consistently below
的g1始终低于
500 milliseconds that literally means
500毫秒，字面意思是
that sometimes we would be worse than
有时候我们会比
this right well be way outside the ring
这是正确的方式
and typical positives will be in the
而典型的积极因素将在
tens of milliseconds literally means we
数十毫秒的字面意思是我们
will have pawns it's much bigger in
将有典当它在更大
intensive milliseconds we told you so
如此密集的毫秒
right so these are good ways to make you
对，所以这些都是让你成功的好方法
feel good about but if you actually have
感觉很好但是如果你真的有
to make an application live in the real
使应用程序真实存在
world you might want to actually measure
您可能想要实际测量的世界
what's going on and get enough open
这是怎么回事，并获得足够的开放
source everything and it lets you if you
采购一切，如果您
the actual Higa thing behavior of your
您的实际Higa事物行为
application oh we are so it's not 15
应用程序哦，我们不是15
minutes
分钟
I'll do two more minutes than a quick
我要快两分钟
sorry about this
为此事道歉
so c4 is a collector we have it solved
所以c4是一个收集器，我们已经解决了
this problem the problems solving you
这个问题解决你的问题
can look up the slides online later but
可以稍后在线查找幻灯片，但是
fundamentally if you classify it it has
从根本上说，如果对它进行分类
a great guaranteeing single pass marker
极好的保证单程标记
can't be done concurrent compactor it
无法完成并发压缩
classifies as compacting a concurrent
分类为压缩并发
collecting option and the concurrent
收集选项和并发
compacting Yujin it's the only non
压榨玉金这是唯一的非
pausing new gender is right now and JVMs
现在暂停新性别，JVM
or run times in general it has no
或运行时间通常没有
fallback to stop the world we don't have
后退以阻止我们所没有的世界
code that knows how to do this so there
知道如何执行此操作的代码
is no fool TC there is no stop the wall
没有傻瓜TC没有停止
there's no I couldn't do it so we will
没有我做不到的，所以我们会
pause it stick
停下来坚持
design-wise it's built around the notion
在设计方面，它是围绕该概念构建的
of always doing the same thing and never
总是做同样的事情，从不
being in a hurry a lot of the algorithm
急着很多算法
design is to make sure this is true
设计是要确保这是真的
algorithm cool things you can see this
算法很酷的东西你可以看到这个
online but let's talk about what it does
在线，但让我们谈谈它的作用
to your application the fundamental
对您的应用程序而言
thing is we take care of things like GC
事情是我们照顾像GC这样的事情
tuning so you no longer have to do this
进行调整，因此您不再需要这样做
or this instead you just do this kind of
或者这只是你做这种
stuff and tune the heap size down until
填充并调整堆大小，直到
it breaks and then triple it and go home
它会破裂，然后将其放大三倍然后回家
right so you know tuning GC looks like
对，所以您知道调整GC的样子
this you get behaviors for real
这样你就可以得到真实的行为
applications where this is Cassandra
这是Cassandra的应用程序
running an irregular server that's the
运行一个不规则的服务器
one really second and you get to run
一秒钟，你就可以跑步了
applications with just more throughput
具有更高吞吐量的应用程序
per machine if you care about us a nice
每台机器，如果您在乎我们
you just get more out of a machine if
如果从机器中获得更多收益，
the reason you put more machines to work
您将更多机器投入使用的原因
as SLA isn't good if you put too much
因为如果您投入过多，SLA就不好
work on it so fundamentally that's what
从根本上进行工作就是
c4 does and it is a concurrent
c4确实是并发的
concurrent dumped in an ultra collector
并发倾倒在超级收集器中
you can come to our booth you can come
你可以来我们的展位，你可以来
to be able to hear does I clear that one
能够听到我是否清除了一个
for the next speaker and I'm sorry for
下一位发言者，对不起
the surprise at the time here I thought
我以为当时的惊喜
me in another
我在另一个